//creating array and passing the number,questions, options and answers.
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"What is the largest city in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"Colombo",
        options : [ 
            "Kandy",
            "Colombo",
            "Pollonaruwa",
            "Galle"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"What is the highest mountain in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"Pidurutalagala",
        options: [
            "Kirigalpotta",
            "Top Pass Hill",       
            "Hakgala",
            "Pidurutalagala"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Which famous beach town is located on the southern coast of Sri Lanka?",
        answer: "Unawatuna",
        options: [
            "Unawatuna",
            "Hikkaduwa",
            "Weligama",
            "Nilaveli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"What is the most popular national park in Sri Lanka for wildlife safaris?",
        answer:"Yala National Park",
        options: [
            "Kaudulla National Park",
            "Wilpattu National Parka",
            "Minneriya National Park",
            "Yala National Park"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"What is the name of the ancient rock fortress located in central Sri Lanka?", 
        answer:"Sigiriya",
        options: [
            "Yapahuwa rock fortress",
            "Sri Pada / Adam's Peak",
            "Sigiriya",
            "Kudahagala"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"What is the name of the famous Buddhist temple located in Kandy?",
        answer:"Temple of the Tooth",
        options: [
            "Temple of the Tooth",
            "Lankarama",
            "Thuparamaya Dagaba",
            "Mirisavetiya Stupa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"What is the most famous festival in Sri Lanka celebrated annually in July/August?",
        answer:"Esala Perahera (Kandy Perahera)",
        options: [
            "Maha Shivaratri Day",
            "Vesak Poya",
            "Sinhala and Tamil New Year's",
            "Esala Perahera (Kandy Perahera)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Which famous tea-growing region in Sri Lanka is located in the central highlands?",
        answer:"Nuwara Eliya",
        options: [
            "Badulla",
            "Nuwara Eliya",
            "Kandy",
            " Kegalle"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"What is the name of the famous 17th century Dutch fort located in Galle",
        answer:"Galle Fort",
        options: [
            "Ruwanwella fort",
            "Balana Fort",
            "Galle Fort",
            "Matara Fort"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"What is the name of the famous train ride that goes through the tea country in Sri Lanka?",
        answer:"The Kandy to Ella train ride",
        options: [
            "Colombo to Kandy",
            "Kandy to Badulla",
            "Anuradhapura to Jaffna",
            "The Kandy to Ella train ride"
        ]
    },     
];